("Jessie's Girl" by Rick Springfield)
♪ Jessie is a friend ♪
♪ Yeah I know he's been
a good friend of mine ♪
♪ But lately something's changed
that ain't hard to define ♪
♪ Jessie's got himself a girl
and I want to make her mine ♪
♪ And she's watching him with those eyes ♪
♪ And she's loving him with
that body I just know it ♪
♪ Yeah and he's holding her in
his arms late late at night ♪
♪ You know I wish that I had ♪
♪ Jessie's girl ♪
♪ I wish that I had Jessie's girl ♪
♪ Where can I find a woman like that ♪
♪ I'll play along with the charade ♪
♪ There doesn't seem to
be a reason to change ♪
♪ You know I feel so dirty
when they start talking cute ♪
♪ I wanna tell her that I love her ♪
♪ But the point is probably moot ♪
♪ 'Cause she's watching
him with those eyes ♪
♪ And she's loving him with
that body I just know it ♪
♪ And he's holding her in
his arms late late at night ♪
♪ You know I wish that I had ♪
♪ Jessie's girl ♪
♪ I wish that I had Jessie's girl ♪
♪ Where can I find a woman like that ♪
♪ Like Jessie's girl ♪
♪ I wish that I had Jessie's girl ♪
♪ Where can I find a woman ♪
♪ Where can I find a woman like that ♪
♪ And I'm looking in the
mirror all the time ♪
♪ Wonderin' what she don't see in me ♪
♪ I've been funny I've
been cool with the lines ♪
♪ Ain't that the way
love's supposed to be ♪
♪ Tell me where can I
find a woman like that ♪
♪ You know I wish that I had ♪
♪ Jessie's girl ♪
♪ I wish that I had Jessie's girl ♪
♪ I want Jessie's girl ♪
♪ Where can I find a woman like that ♪
♪ Like Jessie's girl ♪
♪ I wish that I had Jessie's girl ♪
♪ I want I want Jessie's girl ♪